Finding Aid for the C. Rick Chappell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, September –October 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- National Science Foundation –Science and Engineering Indicators Review, October 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- National Science Foundation –Potential Proposal, March 2001 –June 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, February 2000 –March 2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- National Science Foundation –Proposal, June 2000 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, August –September 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2000 –June 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2000 –June 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, July –; April 2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, February 2000 –May 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, March –September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September –October 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- National Science Foundation –Quickie Planning Grant and Lange Proposal, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, April 2001 –March 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September –; December 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, July –September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- National Science Foundation –TV News Archives Proposal, July –September 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, April 1999 –February 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, January –; March 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, January 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, September 1998 –January 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, September 1998 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, July –September 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, May 1998 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Proposal to Robert Lichter, Director of the Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, August 1997 –April 1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March 5-6 2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Department of Energy –Communication of Scientific Research Concerning Low –Dose Radiation Workshop, March –June 2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, December 2000 –January 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, November 2000 –January 2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, July 2000 –May 2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, March –April 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, March 2000 –March 2001 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, April 2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, May 2000 –February 2001 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, July 1999 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Department of Energy –Back-up Materials, December 1999 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Space Action Network (SPAN) Project, June 2001 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Space Action Network (SPAN) Project, June 2001 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Space Action Network (SPAN) Project, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Research Information Flow/Faculty Contact, December 1999 –March 2001 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Research Information Flow/Faculty Contact, March 1998 –October 1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- American Institute of Physics –Meeting, March 2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Edward E. Smith & Company –Lecture, March 2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- National Association of State Universities and land Grant Colleges –Meeting, June –August 200 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- National Public Health Information Coalition –Meeting, July –September 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- National Public Health Information Coalition –Meeting, August 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- National Public Health Information Coalition –Meeting, September –October 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- National Public Health Information Coalition –Meeting, July –October 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- National Public Health Information Coalition –Meeting, October 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Science Communicators –Media Training (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Science Communicators –Media Training (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Universities Space Research Association, November 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Universities Space Research Association, November 2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Universities Space Research Association –Financial Statement, June 1998 –June 1999 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Marshall Space Flight Center –Class Trip, April 2001 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- American Geophysical Union –Public Information Committee, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry –Partners in Public Health Luncheon, January –April 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry –Partners in Public Health Luncheon, January –April 2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Dyer Observatory Director –Rick Chappell (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Dyer Observatory –Thank Yous (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Virginia Tech University –Personal Papers Donation (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April –June 2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April –June 2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, March –April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, March –April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, February –April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, March 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, January –February 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, November 2001 –April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Research! America –Vanderbilt Science/Media Forum, October –December 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Research! America –Society of Women’s Health Research –Scientist Media Panel, July –August 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Research! America –Society of Women’s Health Research –Scientist Media Panel, July –August 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Research! America –Society of Women’s Health Research –Scientist Media Panel, July –August 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Research! America –Society of Women’s Health Research –Scientist Media Panel, July –August 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Research! America –Washington D.C., May –July 2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Research! America –Emory University –Scientist Media Roundtable, May; June 2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Research! America –University of Las Vegas –Scientist Media Roundtable, June 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Research! America –Society for Neuroscience Annual Meeting –Media Scientist Roundtable, November 2000 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Research! American –Case Western University –Scientist Media Roundtable, September –October 2000 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Images of Exploration –Book –John Denver, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Mayo Clinic Trip, June –July 2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Mayo Clinic Trip, September 2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Sun –Earth Connection –Meeting with NASA ISSAT Committee, September 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- NASA Astrobiology Focus Group, November 2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Future NASA Outreach Grant, September 2002 –August 2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Ellen Fanning/Howard Hughes Medical Institute Visit, April 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Correspondence –Personal, June 2005 –January 2008 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Marshall Space Flight Center –Interactions, November 2006 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity, January 2005 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Emmy Presentation, November 2008 –January 2009 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Emmy Presentation, November 2008 –January 2009 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Overhead projector transparencies (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Overhead projector transparencies (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Overhead projector transparencies (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Overhead projector transparencies (Box 21, Folder 1)